{
    "subject": "resource/Laza_Ristovski",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "Serbian musician",
    "human_readable": "Laza Ristovski is a Serbian musician.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9464895129203796,
            "question": "What type of musician is Laza Ristovski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8605098724365234,
            "question": "Is Laza Ristovski known for his work in music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8283332586288452,
            "question": "Is there information available about Laza Ristovski's musical style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7987516522407532,
            "question": "What is Laza Ristovski known for in the music world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7575135231018066,
            "question": "Has Laza Ristovski achieved recognition for his musical work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7268490791320801,
            "question": "Where is Laza Ristovski from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6865450739860535,
            "question": "What nationality is Laza Ristovski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6861155033111572,
            "question": "What country is Laza Ristovski associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6824518442153931,
            "question": "What profession does Laza Ristovski have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6670111417770386,
            "question": "Does Laza Ristovski perform any other profession besides music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Laza Ristovski is a Serbian musician.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1051_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does Laza Ristovski have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1051_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Laza Ristovski associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1051_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Laza Ristovski?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1051_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1051_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1051_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1051_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1051_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1051_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1051_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1051_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1051_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1051_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1051_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Laza Ristovski being a Serbian keyboardist and musician, confirming that he fits the description of a Serbian musician."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}